

Dhanashri Sutar

UI/ UX Designer

CONTACT

- 7219012510
- ☑ sutardhanashri10@gmail.com
- Pune, Maharashtra 411043

PERSONAL DETAILS

Birth Date: 10. 05. 1991 Material Status: Married

Languages: Marathi, Hindi, English

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Adobe XD

Figma

Balsamiq

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Photoshop

Corel Draw

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Research

Card Sorting

Personas

Wire-framing

Low to High Fidelity Design

Prototyping

Sketching

Painting

HOBBIES

Music

Dance

Tree Planting

MY WORK & PROFILE

- behance.net/dhanashris4456
- linkedin.com/in/dhanashri-sutara68364152/
- github.com/

ABOUT ME

I have 1 year of experience as a UI/UX Designer & have a 3 years of experience as a Graphic Designer, during which I developed skills in creating visual designs for various mediums such as digital media. I strongly understand UI UX & Design principles such as typography, color theory, layout, and composition.

EDUCATION

2009. S.S.C - Bharti Vidyapeeth, Pune

2011. Foundation- Bharti Vidyapeeth, Pune

2016. Commercial Diploma- Abhinav Kala Mahavidyalay

WORK EXPERIENCE

June 2017

Graphic Designer, Jigyasa

Social Media Post Designer. Tools use - Adobe Photoshop

June 2018-June 2020

Associate - Designer, Affinity X Pune

Digital Design Campaigns

Tools use - Adobe Photoshop,

Website name Flexitive Animation done for Social Media Digital Post

Jan 2021

Freelancer Bitty Solutions Pvt Ltd

Brand: Lorecia social media designs and many more

Aug 2021-22

Felix-it Systems

UI UX Designer

Aug 2022-23

Fitmat Smart Solutions PVT. LTD

UI UX Designer

Project Work

Project Name: Company Branding (Yipli & Kreedalabs)

About Project: Visiting Card, Letterhead, Social Media Post, LinkedIn Post

Tools & Responsibility: Photoshop, Figma, Illustrator

Project Name: Online Learning

About Project: Online learning you can teach by creating courses according

to your skill and if you want to learn

Tools & Responsibility: Adobe XD, Balsamic, Photo-shop & UI UX Designer

Project Name: Olympic Game

About Project: This game based on word Olympic Game and work on mat like

100m Dash, Archery,

Tools & Responsibility: Adobe XD, Balsamic, Photo-shop & UI UX Designer